Signing Agent III

ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99
Email: info@qwikresume.com
Website: www.qwikresume.com
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/qwikresume
Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama

Objective

Seeking a career in Mortgage and Business Development. Notable assets: Loan Origination proficient, and detail-oriented professional with more than 5 years of combined experience. Possess exceptional research and analysis abilities, as well as written and verbal communication, interpersonal relations, and customer service skills. and developed client portfolios.

Skills

MS Office, Management.

Work Experience

Signing Agent III

Independent Loan Servicing - August 2008 - 2020

- Responsible for Residential closings and Commercial investments.
- Works from home via the internet and email.
- Meets with clients in the comfort of their home or a mutually agree location to complete loan signing.
- Provides vendor relations throughout the US with Title Companies, Banks, Mortgage Companies, and Signing Services for personalized loan servicing and customer service for borrower(s).
- Assembles loan package, Identify client and signature authenticity, notarize documents, and return documents to Lender.
- Responsible for NSA (Notary Signing Agent) servicing HELOC, Purchase, Re-Fi, and Respa.
- Responsible for Member of NNA (National Notary Association) and various signing services.

Signing Agent

Delta Corporation - 2007 - 2008

- Steamboat Springs, CO, 2010 to 2012 Notary Public Developed custom electronic spreadsheets for small businesses Signing Agent for the mortgage .
- Coordinated and scheduled multiple loan closings per day with title companies, buyers, and other loan recipients throughout U.S., working with .
- Served as face of company with client title companies, developing strong relationships to provide optimum service and ensuring scheduling and .
- Managed schedules of three additional remotely located signing agents, ensuring continual coverage across all time zones.
- Recruited, interviewed, and hired notaries as closers.
- Safe Act registrant NMLS #1310947 Conduct on site mortgage loan signing for mortgage and title companies.
- Deliver compiled loan package to the borrower(s) for signing, notarization, and return completely and correctly.

Education

Business Computer Information Systems - 1989(University of Houston)